(Leonard:)This is going to decide who's
the hero and who's the sidekick?
(Howard:)You got a better idea?
(Leonard:)Every idea is better
than this idea.
(Howard:)Ding!
Wait. What the hell is "ding"?
It's a bell.
(Raj:)I don't think this
kind of wrestling has a bell.
(Howard:)Fine. How do you
want to start?
(Raj:)I say, uh, how about
one, two, three, go?
(Howard:)One-two-three-go?
That's for babies.
(Raj:)Okay, how about, uh...
(Raj:)On your mark, get set, go?
(Howard:)That's for a footrace.
If you want to race,
(Howard:)we have to go outside.
(Raj:)No, it's chilly outside.
Didn't bring my jacket.
(Howard:)Oh, for crying out loud.
(Howard:)What kind of superhero
needs a jacket?
(Raj:)What kind of superhero says,
"Dibs on the red tights!
Dibs on the red tights!"
(Howard:)All right, how about this?
Ready, wrestle.
(Raj:)Wait. Are we starting now? Or
is that what you're going to say
(Raj:)when we do start, or...
We're starting now!
(Raj:)Don't yell at me!